genyoutube.net 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy - GenYoutube

#### What information do we collect?

We donot collect any kind of information.

#### Do we use cookies?

We do use cookies but over SSL only.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using [this contact form](https://www.genyoutube.net/contact.html).

GenYoutube is a fast Youtube video downloader service. Now download videos in all formats from Youtube using GenYoutube video downloader. Using GenYoutube you can download any type of videos from the Youtube. 

Using it you can search the videos also and can play them too before downloading. You can even search the episodes and movies and download them. Search results can the sorted on the basis of relevance, view count, title, rating and publish date. 

Now you can download songs, movies, episodes, trailers, clips or any Youtube video without visitng the Youtube site with hassle free controls and beautiful responsive UI. Currently It supports 55 formats of video downloads. 

GenYoutube provides Youtube video downloads in mp4, webm, m4a, 3gp and 3D formats which ranges from mobile friendly to HDTV resolution. It can download Vevo videos, age-restricted videos, region protected videos. It also supports new formats which recently Youtube rolled out. GenYoutube is based on super fast script which can handle a number of downloads simultaneously. So you will never any downloading speed issue. So enjoy downloading videos from Youtube using GenYoutube and showcase, watch and listen to the ocean of never ending digital video download stream.
